This document is purely for containment of deleted portions of text which might be useful in the future.

"To gather substantial or definitive proof of Folk theorem in repeated games, by identifying Nash equilibria at different points of the subgames. 
This will be done by measuring the payoffs of weights in the final neural network, which will initially start as random."
^ Might be useful for the introductory section of the dissertation.

"To investigate the blending of multiple fields – in this case, game theory, machine learning and evolutionary algorithms. 
This will lead on to questions regarding the findings being applied to more complex games."
^ General Point

\subsubsection{Kakutani's Fixed Point Theorem}
The Kakutani fixed point theorem states that a common fixed point exists within a collection of maps defined on non-empty, 
convex and compact subsets. Given the following scenario: \\

\noindent
\textit{"Let M be a compact, convex subset of Euclidean n-space. \footnote{A Euclidean space is sometimes known as n-space, and is 
simply the space of all n-tuples of real numbers.} Let T be a continuous set-valued function on M; i.e., a mapping from M to the set of all 
subsets of M, T→P(M). If T is such that T(x) is convex for all x belonging to M then there exists a z such that T(z) contains z."} 
(Kakutani, 1941, p. 457-459) \\

\noindent
This theorem can be proven if the following conditions are satisfied:

\begin{itemize}
  \item M is a non-empty, convex and compact set.
  \item T(x) is non-empty for all x ∈ M.
  \item For all x ∈ M, T(x) is a convex set.
  \item T(x) has a closed graph, i.e. if \{x\textsuperscript{n}, y\textsuperscript{n}\} → \{x, y\} with 
y\textsuperscript{n} ∈ T(x\textsuperscript{n}), then y ∈ T(x).
\end{itemize}

\noindent
If satisfied, a fixed point exists within T. \\

\noindent
The Kakutani theorem is a more generalised proof of the Brouwer fixed point theorem, but is used to prove a Nash equilibrium in a very 
similar way. The conditions used in both theorems can be modified in such a way that you would prove the existence of an equilibrium state 
rather than a fixed point, within a set of strategies rather than tuples. \\
^ Deleted Literature Review Section